gomobi.info 2015-12-05

# Privacy Policy

Last Modified: 17/05/13

Afilias Technologies Limited ("we", "us" and/or "our") 

Please read this privacy statement carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it.

## 1\. Your acceptance of our privacy statement

By accessing and/or using this website, you (including, for the avoidance of doubt, any entity or person on whose behalf you are acting) explicitly agree to the privacy statement set out below and agree that you fully understand it.

If you do not agree, or are not comfortable, with any aspect of this privacy statement, your only option and remedy is to immediately discontinue use of this website.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement from time to time without notice to you. Each time you access and/or use this website you will be bound by the then current privacy statement. For this reason, you should review the privacy statement each time you access and/or use this website.

## 2\. Introduction

We fully respect your right to privacy and are committed to protecting it.

Any personal information which you submit via the website will be treated in accordance with the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003 and this privacy statement.

Some of the technical terms used in this privacy statement are explained at the bottom of this page.

## 3\. External websites

This website contains links to external websites. We are not responsible for and cannot control the content or privacy practices of other websites. These websites may have their own privacy policies and we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal information to their websites.

## 4\. Use of Internet

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure. Further, communicating via the Internet and other electronic means necessarily involves personal information passing through or being handled by third parties such as our Internet service provider.

Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to our website; any transmission is at your own risk. We will implement security procedures once your personal information is received.

## 5\. Collection and use of personal information by us

In order to provide product information, trials and order fulfillment, we collect personal details from you. Such information is used by us for the purpose for which you provided it. We are not in a position to establish whether your personal information is accurate or up-to-date and cannot, therefore, be responsible for doing so. Any information which you provide in this way is not made available to any third parties, and is used by us for internal business purposes only. We do not store customer Credit Card information, this information will be stored by our payment gateway company who will store it on their secure payment gateway for as long as necessary to carry out the terms of your subscription.

## 6\. Direct Marketing Material

From time to time we may contact you with information regarding promotions, ancillary products and our company Newsletters via email. However, you will have the choice to opt in or out of receiving such communications by indicating so at purchase. You will also be given the opportunity on every electronic communication that we send you to indicate that you no longer wish to receive our direct marketing material.

## 7\. Disclosure of personal information

We do not disclose any information which you submit via the website to any third parties without your consent (unless obliged or permitted to disclose such information by a rule of law).

You acknowledge and agree that in certain circumstances we may be obliged to disclose personal information you submit to third parties, for example, in order to conform to any requirements of law or to comply with any legal process, as well as to protect and defend our rights.

We reserve the right to transfer ownership of the website (including personal information you submit) to a third party in the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, receivership or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of us, a subsidiary or line of business associated with us.

## 8\. Use of cookies

This website does not use cookies except to enable our system to remember whether or not a user has used its password to log in. This is to help us improve our website. It enables the system to automatically log out users after a certain period of time or force the user to log in again if the user closes the web page and then starts it up again. This is to prevent third parties from gaining unauthorised access to a user’s account and is for users’ own protection.

You should note that technical details which we cannot associate with any identifiable individual do not constitute "personal data" for the purposes of the Data Protection Acts 1988 and 2003.

Save as mentioned above, no information is collected by the use of cookies that could be used by us to identify website users.

You may refuse to accept cookies by activating the setting on your browser which allows you to refuse the setting of cookies. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our website. Unless you have adjusted your browser so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you log on to our website.

Please note that third party external websites to which we provide links (over which we have no control and do not stand over in any way) may also use cookies.

## 9\. Internet Advertising

Third party vendors, such as Google, may show our ads on sites on the Internet. Third party vendors, such as Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. Users can opt out of cookies used by Google for advertising. You can opt out by:

  * **Opting out of DoubleClick cookies:** Users can opt out of DoubleClick cookies by visiting the [DART Ad-Serving and Search Cookie Opt-Out](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx) page.
  * **Opting out of Google advertising cookies:** Users can opt out of Google's use of cookies for advertising by visiting Google's [Advertising and Privacy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) page.
  * **Opting out of cookies from all participating advertisers:** Users can opt out of third-party advertising cookies from a wide range of advertising services, including Google, by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative's Opt-Out page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

## 10\. Your rights

You have a right to be given a copy of your personal data which is held by us. We may charge a fee for this which will not exceed €10.

You also have a right to have inaccurate personal information relating to you which is held by us corrected. In certain circumstances, you may also request the deletion of your personal information held by us. To exercise this right you would generally be expected to identify some contravention of data protection law in the manner in which we process the data concerned. We will deal with any such requests within the statutory timeframe.

To exercise any of these rights, please contact us using the email subject or letter subject ‘Data Protection / Legal’ at:  
Afilias Technologies,  
4th Floor, International House,  
3 Harbourmaster Place,  
IFSC,  
Dublin 1,  
Ireland   
E-mail: dublin-legal [at} afilias.info

You should include with any such request any personal identifiers which you supplied earlier via the website (e.g. name; address; phone number; e-mail address, password) or otherwise.

We reserve the right to request you to provide additional information in order to enable us to identify your personal information and/or to verify your identity. If such information is required, this may affect the timeline within which we deal with your request.

## 11\. Security

We take our security responsibilities seriously, employing appropriate physical, organisational and technical measures. We review our security policy regularly.

## 12\. Governing law and jurisdiction

This privacy statement and all issues regarding this website are governed by Irish law and are subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the Irish courts.

## 13\. Contacting us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, our practices relating to this website or your dealing with this website you can contact us at the following address:

E-mail: dublin-legal [at} afilias.info

## 14\. Glossary of Technical Terms

Cookies: Small pieces of information, stored in simple text files, placed on your computer by a website. Cookies can be read by the website on your subsequent visits. The information stored in a cookie may relate to your browsing habits on the web page, or a unique identification number so that the website can "remember" you on your return visit. Generally speaking, cookies do not contain personal information from which you can be identified, unless you have furnished such information to the website.

Thank you for visiting our website.

This is the website of Afilias Technologies Ltd, a private company limited by shares, incorporated and registered in the Republic of Ireland with registered number 398040 and registered office at First Floor, Fitzwilton House, Wilton Place, Dublin 2, Ireland.

Copyright © 2015 Afilias Technologies Ltd (dotMobi)

This is a website of Afilias Technologies Ltd, a private company limited by shares, incorporated and registered in the Republic of Ireland with registered number 398040 and registered office at Sixth Floor, 2 Grand Canal Square, Dublin 2, Ireland.
